easyvoyage.co.uk 2016-12-05

# Easyvoyage newsletter

## The Easyvoyage newsletters.

Easyvoyage newsletters are published by the company EASYVOYAGE SAS - stock company with a capital of €300,999. Registered offices: 2, rue Paul Vaillant Couturier 92300 Levallois Perret, France. RCS Nanterre B 432 123 446 and represented by the CEO Jean-Pierre Nadir.

The Easyvoyage newsletters contain a selection of online offers and information for which users can subscribe to, for free. The incorporation of user data relating to the Easyvoyage newsletter comes from the users' prior consent, collected (1) on websites published by Easyvoyage, (2) by carrying out competitions, or (3) via Easyvoyage's partner websites.

Once subscribed, each user will regularly receive offers via Easyvoyage newsletters.

## Easyvoyage and the protection of your personal data.

The charter aims to define, firstly, the various personal data collected from you by Easyvoyage for its newsletters, and secondly, the measures we take to protect your personal data.

By subscribing to the Easyvoyage newsletters, you authorise us to establish, maintain and update a file of the personal information you have provided us with, whilst understanding that this file is limited to your registration information (first name, surname, email address, etc.).

In order to render the services to which you have subscribed, your personal information will be shared with all companies belonging to the Easyvoyage Group (hereafter the ‘Group’) and to their commercial providers and partners. You will be informed of any offers, events and news which they consider will be of interest to you, based on the preferences (agreement or refusal) that you provide when you subscribe and which you can modify at any time. In accordance with the French law entitled “Informatique & Libertés”, you can request access to the personal information you provided, in order to modify, rectify or delete any part of it, by writing to us at [contactuk@easyvoyage.fr](mailto:%63%6F%6E%74%61%63%74%75%6B%40%65%61%73%79%76%6F%79%61%67%65%2E%66%72) or at the following address: Easyvoyage, 2 rue Paul Vaillant-Couturier 92300 Levallois-Perret, FRANCE

The treatment of personal data used with regard to Easyvoyage newsletters are registered with the National Commission for Computing and Liberties under the number 1298016.

We are committed to protecting Your privacy and will not disclose personal information about You to any third party in the strict context of what is stated in this Privacy Policy. We will ensure that the storage and use of this information is consistent with existing laws on the protection of privacy in France.
